(
"ai_sub_version": "1.11.0",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 3,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
ホロライブファンクラブ！
Hololive Fan Club!
一条莉々華だよ！
I'm Ichijou Ririka!
I'm Mori Calliope.
ホロライブファンクラブ始めました！
The Hololive Fan Club has started!
ここだけのオリジナルグッズや
Original goods only available here,
チケット先行抽選、
early ticket lotteries,
他にも楽しいコンテンツがいっぱい！
and lots of other fun content!
Campaigns too?
That sounds really fun. I'm curious!
さぁ、みんな！ホロライブファンクラブで
Now, everyone! Let's have fun together
一緒に楽しもう！
at the Hololive Fan Club!
Join us now!
ここは露天風呂が有名だって言うから
They say the open-air baths here are famous,
ずっと気になってたんだよね～！
so I've been curious for a long time!
……ね、キミも一緒に行かない？
...Hey, won't you come with me?
えっ！？一緒に貼入って
Eh!? I didn't mean
意味じゃないよ！？
entering together!?
おーそーじ！モココ、
Big cleanup! Mococo
大掃除をやってみたいんだよね！
wants to try doing a big cleanup!
もちろんキミも一緒にやるんだよ！？
Of course, you're doing it with me too!?
じゃあ早速大掃除、
Then let's start the big cleanup
開始だ～！
right away!
え～？
Eh~?
服のすきまがどうしたって～？
What's wrong with the gap in my clothes~?
僕が掃除している間に、キミはいったい
I wonder where you were looking
どこを見てたのかな～？
while I was cleaning~?
お～！ここが夢にまで見た
Oh~! This is the Japanese hot spring town
日本の温泉街～♪
I've dreamed of~♪
ん？もしかして……私と
Hmm? By any chance... are you thinking
一緒に入りたいなとか、思ってる？
you want to enter with me?
……いいよ、
...Sure,
一緒に入ろっか……？
shall we go in together...?
……って、やばいやばい！みんな、
...Wait, oh no oh no! Everyone,
そろそろカウントダウン始まるよ！
the countdown is about to start!
５！
5!
４！
4!
３！
3!
２！
2!
１！
1!
０！
0!
ハッピーニューイヤー！！
Happy New Year!!
あけましておめでとうございます！
Happy New Year!
今年もよろしくお願いします！
Please treat me well this year too!
えへへ……なんかあらためてかしこまると、
Ehehe... getting formal like this
はずかしくて照れちゃうね♪
is a bit embarrassing and makes me blush♪
ダイヤモンド富士っていうんだっけ？
Is it called Diamond Fuji?
ほらほら！だんだん富士山の輪郭が見えてきたよ！
Look, look! The outline of Mt. Fuji is appearing!
なんだかもう、この景色だけで感動するよ～！
Somehow, just this view alone is moving~!
突然ですが、おせちを 作りまーす！
This is sudden, but I'm going to make osechi!
つまみ食いしちゃだめだよ？
No snacking, okay?
もしつまみ食いしちゃったら……バウバウ！
If you snack... Bau wau!
ガブッてしちゃうからねっ！？
I'll bite you!?
おめでとー！おめでとー！
Happy New Year! Happy New Year!
キミとぎゅーしながらお祝い♪
Celebrating while hugging you♪
キミをぎゅーできるのはモココだけなんだから！
Only Mococo can hug you!
ほらほらキミも
Come on, you
モココのことぎゅーってして！
hug Mococo too!
せーの！
One, two!
今年もよろしくお願いします！
Please treat us well this year too!
再販！ゆくホロ2023！くるホロ2024！
Resale! Yuku Holo 2023! Kuru Holo 2024!
ホロ新春ゲーム祭 2026
Holo New Year Game Festival 2026
夢の途中の
In the middle of a dream
一瞬一瞬を、
Every single moment,
一緒に大切に。
Let's cherish them together.
過去最大規模の
The largest scale ever
「そらぱ」がいま始まる。
of "Sorapa" begins now.
ホロライブ3期生
hololive 3rd Generation
次に挑む舞台は
The next stage they challenge...
大作戦？
A grand strategy?
＃きゆるるん大作戦 ～最強アイドルに推すしかないでしょ～
#Kyururun Grand Strategy ~You Have No Choice But to Support the Strongest Idols~
「好き」と「かわいい」を詰め込んで、あなたと作る大作戦！
Packed with "love" and "cute", a grand strategy to build with you!
いっぱいのこれまでと、ときめくような一瞬を！
With all our moments so far, and a heart-pounding instant!
どこまででも行けちゃう気がする
I feel like I can go anywhere
ちなみに作戦の内容は
By the way, the contents of the strategy...
とにかくかわいい！かわいいに満たされろ！
Are just "cute"! Be filled with "cute"!
作戦進行中！
Strategy in progress!
＃ホロ新春3期生24時間配信
#Holo New Year 3rd Gen 24-Hour Stream
正月衣装お披露目リレー
New Year Outfit Reveal Relay
NEW VOICE PACK Coming Soon
まもなく配信開始します
Broadcasting soon
FG ROADSTER
作詞：ボトムムギン
作曲：ボトムムギン / LUNA / Joe Ogawa / Foux
編曲：Foux
FG ROADSTER
Lyrics: Bottumgin
Music: Bottumgin / LUNA / Joe Ogawa / Foux
Arrangement: Foux
This is FLOW GLOW in COUNTDOWN LIVE! 来年もよろしく！
This is FLOW GLOW in COUNTDOWN LIVE! Best wishes for next year!
Let's go 搭載 V8エンジン
Let's go, equipped with a V8 engine
第7感 持ってる言辞
My 7th sense, the words I hold
ロックする この世界と全人類
Locking down this world and all of humanity
この5人でゲームはチェンジ
With these five, the game is changing
鳴る4輪発射セヨ
Sound off, launch those four wheels
皆さんサンキューサランヘヨ
Thank you and Saranghae to everyone
エグいニタイのタンテボ
Crazy dual turntables
ホロ一番カッコいいブランド0
The coolest brand in hololive, Brand 0
Hey! リスク超えて挑戦
Hey! Challenge beyond the risks
チャンスもセットだ当然
Of course, chances come as a set
上り詰める頂点
Climbing to the peak
座布団積んでいけSHOW TIME
Stack those cushions, it's SHOW TIME
打ち込めFGロードスター
Drive it in, FG Roadster
特殊部隊集合能力者
Special forces assembly, ability users
この歴史に残るここから
From here, making history
ぶっちぎりで置き去り攻略者
Pulling ahead, leaving everyone behind, conquerors
いま高速でぶち抜いていく大気圏
Now piercing through the atmosphere at high speed
エンジンからジェットの咆哮入れている快気鋭
Switching from engine to jet roar, feeling exhilarated
満開に広がる大地越えていく快気晴
Over the vast blooming land, a refreshing spirit
バックミラーにビッグブルーが映ってるI'll be there
The Big Blue is reflected in the rearview mirror, I'll be there
FIRE! 打ち明けたいから
FIRE! Because I want to speak out
飛んでいくうちら世代
Our generation is flying away
この燃料 朽ち果てないぜ
This fuel will never die out
ギンギラギンに過ごしてたい
I want to live shining brilliantly
見えてるデッカいビジョン
Seeing a huge vision
燃えてるメンバー一等
Burning members are number one
ただいま現在進行形
Right now, in progress
超えてく世界規模
Crossing over on a global scale
かませハッスルモンスター
Bring it on, Hustle Monster
心臓がマスター
The heart is the master
エリアは全部手中に
The entire area is in our hands
FG PARTY HIGH
光るテスラロードスター
Shining Tesla Roadster
ヘビーブースター目覚めていく本能
Heavy Booster, awakening instincts
青い炎を
Blue flames
V.I.P Let's go out
騒げin the CAR 0から
Make some noise in the CAR, from zero
空まで 捕らわれ
To the sky, captive
走るFGロードスター
Driving the FG Roadster
唸るブースター
The roaring booster
FLOW GLOW The space to be
今 チェイスミー
Now chase me
飛ばすぜスーパーカー
Speeding in the supercar
半端ねぇ様相 急所もハンパ
Incredible appearance, even the weak points are crazy
110重症 中盤か
Serious condition, 110? Is it the middle?
次元が違うぜ連中ばっか
Everyone's on a different level
Ayy! 今な攻めてるギリギリ
Ayy! Attacking right at the limit now
モーター全開ビキビキ
Motor at full throttle, vroom vroom
空から導き
Guidance from the sky
お花がピチピチ
Flowers are sparkling
タイヤ焦がしてドーナツターン
Burning tires, donut turn
弾け飛んでいくドラム缶
Drum cans flying everywhere
顧客満足度高くて
High customer satisfaction
ぶち上がってるおきゃくさん
The audience is getting pumped up
0から最高到達点
Reaching the highest point from zero
溜めてる太陽光発電
Storing solar power
探索するこの小惑星
Exploring this asteroid
超覚醒突入ボーナスデー
Bonus day, entering super awakening
一直線伸びてる道路
A road stretching out in a straight line
バイブレーションエンジンの鼓動
Vibration, the heart of the engine
速度増し上がってる鼓動
Heartbeat increasing with speed
限界重力凌駕上昇
Rising, surpassing the limit of gravity
開拓しまくってくフロンティア
Continuing to pioneer the frontier
旅立つロックスター オンリーワン
A rockstar setting out, the only one
アクセル踏み込んでくドンピシャ
Stepping on the gas perfectly
飛んでいく日本 遺産
A legacy flying through Japan
強欲バリキの充填オン
Filling on with greedy horsepower
火星の果てまで休憩場
Rest stops all the way to the edge of Mars
並んで走行UFO
Running alongside UFOs
降り立つ宇宙ステーション
Landing at the space station
物語を継承
Inheriting the story
まるで公約聖書
Like a public bible
この先何世紀も成長
Growing for many centuries to come
生き延びて結果だ 成功
Surviving and achieving results, success
かませハッスルモンスター
Bring it on, Hustle Monster
心臓がマスター
The heart is the master
エリアは全部手中に
The entire area is in our hands
FG PARTY HIGH
光るテスラロードスター
Shining Tesla Roadster
ヘビーブースター目覚めていく本能
Heavy Booster, awakening instincts
青い炎を
Blue flames
V.I.P Let's go out
騒げin the CAR 0から
Make some noise in the CAR, from zero
空まで 捕らわれ
To the sky, captive
走るFGロードスター
Driving the FG Roadster
唸るブースター
The roaring booster
FLOW GLOW The space to be
FLOW GLOW, THE SPACE TO BE
今 チェイスミー
Now, chase me
以上、私たち、FLOW GLOWでしたー！
That was us, FLOW GLOW!
こっから先も、楽しんでいこうー！
Let's keep having fun from here on out!
Tame the fire and fall before my justice
Final warning, you know my rage is limitless
On the advent of a new genesis
I'm infamous, yeah I get a little villainous
Look into my eyes, I’ll take you on a rebel ride
To realize that you just can’t hide
Clawing at the walls, I feel these sick temptations
What do I have to sacrifice?
Bound by chains, desiring to do it my way
This hurricane of a devastating force is coming
Out of the maze, feel my pulse rising and igniting
Fire, earth, snuff it out
Walking the line on the edge of becoming
What I never thought I’d be better, this standard gonna
Take them all out, Renegade
Walking the line fell so far into poison
And I see-ni-ya, now I gotcha, locked and I’m loading
Take them all out, Renegade
Justice is just like that
I don’t care at all, I’ll go deeper until I can’t quit
Never gonna stop cause I don’t have a limit
My moral compass is out of focus, Renegade
Don’t make it a little bit
The light goes out (Ha!)
The light goes out (Uh!)
The light goes out (Ha-ah!)
The light goes out
Make them fall down, make them, make them last switch
Make them, make them fall down in the crash, Renegade
Bound by broken, everything I desire is never me
Making sound, think of the light of the fire
Burning a mountain followed us and in the ashes
Fire, snuff it out
Walking the line on the edge of becoming
What I never thought I’d be better, this standard gonna
Take them all out, Renegade
Walking the line fell so far into poison
And I see-ni-ya, now I gotcha, locked and I’m loading
Take them all out, Renegade
Justice is just like that
I don’t care at all, I’ll go deeper until I can’t quit
Never gonna stop cause I don’t have a limit
My moral compass is out of focus, Renegade
Don’t make it a little bit
The light goes out (Ha! Yeah!)
The light goes out (Oh, oh, oh!)
The light goes out (Hah!)
The light goes out (Ha!)
Tame the fire and fall before my justice
Final warning, you know my rage is limitless
On the advent of a new genesis
I’m infamous, yeah I get a little villainous
The light goes out
空覚えした人生ゲーム
A life game learned by heart
言い訳めいたハートに従って
Following a heart full of excuses
現実は半世紀空論(ソロ)フロートです
Reality is a half-century empty theory float
取り憑かれるオーバーシュガー・アイ
Obsessed over-sugar eye
夕暮れ時、退屈なあの子はね
At dusk, that bored girl, you see
二度とかぶった猫外せやしない
Can't ever take off the act she put on
瞳(め)をしてしまったマジシャン
A magician who made eye contact
手の内はまだ明かせない
Can't reveal the hand yet
Yellow Yellow ゼロからループで
Yellow Yellow, looping from zero
転滅するピリオド
A period that flickers out
Yellow Yellow 染まる紅い結晶
Yellow Yellow, stained crimson crystals
And if I can make it or not.
酔いが醒めるまで　あと少しだけ
Until I sober up, just a little more
芯のアイ捉える残像
An afterimage that captures the true essence
そう　演じてウィーン・ザ・レース
Yes, performing to win the race
次の季節を乞う　Blooming Blooming
Yearning for the next season, blooming blooming
どうかこの音を止めないで
Please don't stop this sound
OUR TIME YELLOW YELLOW
LOLLIPOP LOLLIPOP　ずっと最高
LOLLIPOP LOLLIPOP, always the best
OUR TIME YELLOW YELLOW
LOLLIPOP LOLLIPOP　LET'S ENJOY THE MOMENT
LOLLIPOP LOLLIPOP, LET'S ENJOY THE MOMENT
Looking into the mirror
絡まってるクモの糸
The tangled spider's web
It happens all the time
踊らされた言葉の罠
The trap of words I was forced to dance to
夜に憑いて時を編んで明けて
Possessed by the night, weaving time until dawn
Always be honest
永遠に変わらないもの
Things that will never change
YELLOW YELLOW 手を取り合えば
YELLOW YELLOW If we hold hands
そこに理由は要らない
No reason is needed there
YELLOW YELLOW 染まる赤色
YELLOW YELLOW Being dyed in red
甘い症状 BAD BAD
Sweet symptoms, BAD BAD
行く末なんて関係ない
The outcome doesn't matter
希望に等しい
Like hope
不条理な運命や人生ごと受け入れ
Accepting the irrational fate and life itself
心機一転さぁ夢見ろ！
A fresh start, now dream on!
ノンストップウェーブ今だけを信じて
Non-stop wave, believe only in now
最後のフィナーレまで共に進め
Let's move forward together until the final finale
酔いが醒めるまで　あと少しだけ
Until I sober up, just a little more
芯のアイ捉える残像
An afterimage that captures the true essence
そう　演じてウィーン・ザ・レース
Yes, performing to win the race
次の季節を乞う　Blooming Blooming
Yearning for the next season, blooming blooming
どうかこの音を止めないで
Please don't stop this sound
OUR TIME YELLOW YELLOW
LOLLIPOP LOLLIPOP　ずっと最高
LOLLIPOP LOLLIPOP, always the best
OUR TIME YELLOW YELLOW
LOLLIPOP LOLLIPOP　LET'S ENJOY THE MOMENT
LOLLIPOP LOLLIPOP, LET'S ENJOY THE MOMENT
まったねー！
See ya!
またねー！
See you later!
楽しかったー！
That was fun!
ReGLOSSでした！バイバーイ！
That was ReGLOSS! Bye-bye!
Don't you open up your eyes
Feel the music start to rise
Got to break the world and let me in
And I know I was meant to be
Living life so fast and free
Try to keep your eyes on me
This is where my story all begins
Living in arbitrary places
Waiting for the breaks to come out
Give it away so easily
I can't get enough
Wings are broad, no limit
Happen to hurt, I'm feeling
Everything go, let's do this
Watch me, watch me, watch me be a diva
I'm gonna raise your fever
Shaking up all the crowd
Making some noise when I'm not allowed
Living my life out loud
I have awakened to wisdom beyond understanding
I keep indulging in my element
Oh oh oh, don't blame me
The way I shine so bright
Oh oh oh, can't help it if I start a fight
Oh oh oh, now pay attention
Cause this is only the beginning
It's our genesis
Come to wreak some havoc
How do you like this pattern?
I'm embracing my madness
Can you hear it?
Whispers banging on your window
Heard them now
Rumors reaching a crescendo
No humble beginning
I'm destined for great things
I'm sure you've heard of me by now
Midnight diamond in the dark side
Heard them now
Daybright take me on a joyride
My crime is my passion
A mayhem in action
I know what day it is
This is our genesis
In search of rave when I misbehave
Take center stage
What the funk commands but you know
I'm gonna get in check
There are loopholes unspoken
The rules can all be broken
I'm mending on a rampage
The world is a blank page
Let's go!
I'm writing my story in flames and in glory
Cause they're gonna know me by name
Tonight
Oh oh oh
It's this my promised land?
The future's in my hands
Bow wow wow wow
Tell me how you like me now
Let’s celebrate the New Year!
Come and watch me, watch me, watch me
Let your voice go and show you how to lose control
You’ve got the free on your mind
Leave all your sense behind
Be outrageous, the chaos is contagious
Come on, you know what time it is
It’s our Genesis!
Time to open up your eyes
Feel the music start to rise
Got to break the world and let me in
I know I was meant to be
Living life so fast and free
Try and keep your eyes on me
This is our beginning
This is our Genesis!
Whispers blowing down your window
Rumours reaching a crescendo
No humble beginning
Authentic amazing
I’m sure you’ve heard of me by now
Midnight, join me to the bright side
Daylight, take me on a joyride
My crime is my passion
A mayhem in action
I know what day it is
This is our Genesis!
You know what time it is?
It’s our Genesis!
Tell me what time it is.
You know what time it is?
It’s our Genesis!
Tell me what time it is.
君に届けたい id:entity voices
I want to reach you, id:entity voices
踏み出した一歩を 踏み出した
I've taken a step, I've taken it
おはよう こんばんは 世界に叫んでみよう
Good morning, good evening, let's shout to the world
本日のライブでは どれの自分を見せるの？
In today's live, which self will I show?
迷い 葛藤 悩んで 好きな自分になれない
Wandering, struggling, worrying, I can't become the self I like
そしてある日 誰かに言われた
And then one day, someone told me
「痛い言葉なんてに 迷っていたいた」
"I was lost in such painful words"
いつも作る笑顔 失わないように
So as not to lose the smile I always put on
これ以上 期待を裏切らないと決めた
I've decided not to disappoint anymore
溢れている 雑踏の中 この声 響けるか
In the overflowing crowd, can this voice reach?
心に 宿る声を 聴いてみてほしいな
I want you to try and listen to the voice dwelling in your heart
これは ずっと 見せたかった自分なんだ
This is the self I've always wanted to show
集まった 声たちが ひとつになる id:entity
The gathered voices become one, id:entity
君が注いで やっとスポットライトに
Because you poured it in, I'm finally in the spotlight
立てるけれど 少しだけ怖くなくなった
I can stand here, and I've become a little less afraid
だってもう 一人じゃない 仲間たちがいるんだ
Because I'm not alone anymore, I have my friends
家族みたいな絆で 違いを認め合えた
With a family-like bond, we could acknowledge our differences
それぞれも 輝き合って
Each of us shining together
ハーモニーを 奏でるかな
I wonder if we'll play a harmony
手を繋いで 共に夢の空の方へ
Let's hold hands, towards the sky of dreams together
精一杯 歓声をあげましょう
Let's give it our all and cheer
幸せを 届けるんだ
We'll deliver happiness
どこにだって 響けよ
Let it echo everywhere
新しい舞台に飛び込んで
Jumping into a new stage
今幕が開くよ
Now the curtain rises
乱舞を奏でれば鳴いて
When I play the wild dance and cry out
ここに集めたこの音色が
This tone I've gathered here
震えるハーモニーになって
Becomes a trembling harmony
心の迷いが消えてゆく
And the hesitation in my heart fades away
これからずっとこの自分のままで
From now on, I'll stay as I am forever
集まった声たちが
The gathered voices
違っても揺るがないと信じて
Believe that even if they're different, they won't waver
ひとつになるアイデンティティ
An identity becoming one
Selamat pagi semua / お疲れ様でした
Good morning everyone / Thanks for your hard work
Selamat malam semua / また会う日まで
Good night everyone / Until the day we meet again
我ら、エデンの星を統べるもの！
We are the rulers of the planet Eden!
秘密結社holoX、見参でござる！
Secret Society holoX has arrived!
Let's go!
機は熟した。
The time is ripe.
2026年を待つ貴様ら、
You lot, waiting for the year 2026,
準備はいいか！
Are you ready?!
Are you ready?
夜が深まる ほらDarkness
The night deepens, look, it's Darkness
ノワールな歌声 ボンデラックス
A noir singing voice, Bon deluxe
縄に従え エドウィンスティン
Obey the rope, Edwins tin
もこにん サムライ ガール
Mokonin Samurai Girl
病み気にしないけど
I don't mind feeling sick, but...
ルー・ベ・ド・シェケシェケ
Lu-be-de-shake-shake
センスでオーケー
With sense, it's okay
気さくなガジジャシガシ
Friendly gajijashigashi
悪の手の平
In the palm of evil's hand
踊りたくなる
Makes you want to dance
ほら君も気づけばノリノリで
See, before you know it, you're in the groove too
どうしようもない
There's nothing to be done
どうしようのまま
Staying just as we are
落ちていく運命
The fate of falling
南無三 しょうがない
Oh well, it can't be helped
もう全部
Already everything
塗り替えよう
Let's repaint it all
XとXとXとXが
X and X and X and X
交差する真ん中で
At the center where they cross
NextとNextとNextとNext 系譜はもう
Next and Next and Next and Next, the lineage is already...
始まってる
Underway
飛びな 飛びな 闇が呼ぶほうへ
Fly, fly towards where the darkness calls
暗国のエクスデス
Dark Country Exodus
混沌としたこの世界を、我らholoX色に塗り替えるのだ！
We shall repaint this chaotic world in holoX colors!
皆の者、続け！
Everyone, follow us!
Yes, My Dark!
突貫！
Charge!
アブソリュート・ダークネス・インフィニティ！
Absolute Darkness Infinity!
来年こそ世界征服！
Next year, world domination for sure!
マダム・ホークアイ
Madam Hawk-eye
はい、今見てる皆さんはもうホロクサーですよ！
Yes, everyone watching now is already a holoXer!
ふぁらりにゅう様！
Fararinyuu-sama!
2026年もずっと一緒だよ！
We'll be together through 2026 as well!
黒井・卍・鏡開き！
Kuroi Manji Kagamibiraki!
一刀両断 叩き斬れ！
Cut them down with a single stroke!
どうしようもない
There's nothing to be done
どうしようのまま
Staying just as we are
落ちていく運命
The fate of falling
南無三 しょうがない
Oh well, it can't be helped
もう全部
Already everything
塗り替えよう
Let's repaint it all
刮目せよ！
Bear witness!
XとXとXとXが 交差する真ん中で
At the center where X, X, X, and X cross
NextとNextとNextとNext 系譜はもう 始まってる
Next and Next and Next and Next, the lineage is already underway
飛びな 飛びな 闇が呼ぶほうへ
Fly, fly towards where the darkness calls
笑うのは
The one who laughs...
ホロエクスデス
Horo Exodus
Run Back 'Round
Up with the moonlight
Down in the streetlights
Looking for a spotlight
Making my move
And I'm running
行くぞ！
Let's go!
Days like a whirlwind
Don't stop coming
Got me in a tailspin
What can I do?
Keep running
行くぞ！
Let's go!
Lost and found, back to where I started
I won't stay down, trust me I can do it
I live life loud, take it to the limit
So stand up proud, now I'm gonna sing it
Oh Run back 'round, it's a new beginning
I run back 'round, got to keep believing
I run back 'round, I know where I'm going
I run back 'round, nothing's gonna stop me now
Oh whoa, oh whoa
I'm gonna run back 'round
Sparks on paper
Dreams in the distance
Got to be relentless
Faster than sound
Keep running
行くぞ！
Let's go!
Locked and loaded, 僕らは explosive
Locked and loaded, we are explosive
Swifter and lighter, 明日もきっと brighter
Swifter and lighter, tomorrow will surely be brighter
Faster than lightning, 浴びる事 exciting
Faster than lightning, getting hit by it is exciting
Come on everybody! It's the new dawn!
Oh Run back 'round, it's a new beginning
I run back 'round, got to keep believing
I run back 'round, I know where I'm going
I run back 'round, nothing's gonna stop me now
Oh whoa, oh whoa
I'm gonna run back 'round
走って、走って、走って
Running, running, running
I'm gonna run back 'round
始まるよ、変わるよ
It's starting, it's changing
Look at a dreams just waitin'
I'm gonna run back 'round
Everybody!
Oh whoa, oh whoa
Everybody, come on!
I'm gonna run back 'round
Oh whoa, oh whoa
Hololive! You guys ready?
To greet the new year? Hell yeah!
No time to waste! Let's get it started!
Slap by Step
感情のフレーバー 駆け抜けて
Flavor of emotion, running through
困難だらけの人生だけど
Even in a life full of difficulties
奔放にスラップして
Slapping wildly
楽しんじゃおう
Let's have fun
Fly like a feather Soaring 立ち塞がる壁なんて
Fly like a feather Soaring, any wall standing in the way
踏み越えなきゃ
I must step over
Fly like a feather Soaring 止まれないんじゃなくて
Fly like a feather Soaring, it's not that I can't stop
止まらないんだ
I won't stop
Step by step 行くぜ 散歩 私なりで
Step by step, I'll go, a stroll in my own way
隙あらばその瞬間 歓声 充満して
Whenever there's a chance, that moment, filled with cheers
1, 2, 3 で心身 リフレッシュして
1, 2, 3, refresh your mind and body
止まらない 現実を更新 ハズレはない
The unstoppable reality being updated, there are no misses
振れ 宇宙(ソラ) 抜いて
Swing it, piercing through the universe
歩く最新式ノダンスフロア
Walking on the latest dance floor
どんな美麗な平手打ちを
What a beautiful slap
今日もハズかしがらないで
Don't be shy today either
にやついた頬に 氷スプラッシュ
An icy splash on those smirking cheeks
Clap your hands and stand up, please!
突き放して もてなせば成る
Push them away and entertain them, and it'll work
それがセオリー
That's the theory
Clap your hands and stand up, please!
死刑宣告を突きつける
Pronouncing the death sentence
さあパーティーのショー！
Now, let's start the party show!
Wearing my tears...
...and my heart...
...both of fear...
Ready to breakthrough!
姿
Appearance
形
Form
違っても同じ思い出
Even if they're different, the same memories
辿ったから
Because we traced them
Slap by step 130歩
Slap by step, 130 steps
私なりで 突きあらば
In my own way, if there's a gap
その瞬間に完全掌握
At that moment, total control
沼にハマっちゃうから
Because you'll fall into the swamp
1 2 3 で深層心理
1 2 3 and the deep subconscious
クラッシュしちゃって
Crash it
今すぐでも 私たちの色に
Even right now, in our colors
染め上げた 世界を見せるよ
We'll show you a world we've dyed
皆様、今年の応援もありがとうですわ！
Everyone, thank you for your support this year too!
ホロIDはもっともっと盛り上がるよ！
HoloID will get even more excited!
ずっと見ててね！
Keep watching us!
来年もよろしくお願いいたします！
We look forward to your continued support next year!
See you next year!
3rd STAGE
皆さん、森カリオペです！
Everyone, it's Mori Calliope!
What's up? hololive English Myth coming right at you for a brand new year!
今年すごい盛り上がったね。
It was really exciting this year.
来年もよろしく！
Looking forward to next year too!
We're gonna rock the world 10 times harder next year. You in?
Next up, Ina!
Wah! Hello everyone! This is Ina!
Thank you so much for a really fun 2025!
今年すっごく楽しかったです！
This year was so much fun!
来年もよろしくお願いしますね！
Looking forward to next year as well!
Yeah, let's go!
Next is Kiara! Wah!
キキリキ！小鳥遊キアラです！
Kikiriki! I'm Takanashi Kiara!
キアラらしく盛り上げるぞー！
I'm gonna liven things up in my own Kiara style!
Dankeschön!
Let's go!
ガッツリやりましょうか！
Let's give it our all!
2026年もよろしく！
Looking forward to 2026 too!
Alright, let's show 'em what we got!
There's an answer out there somewhere
When the muses whisper truth or dare
Hands of fate tug at the world
But no one's keeping score
Set the course and be tenacious
'Cause the future is a game of chance
The chips are down, but I'm a winner
Play until I win
I'm not gonna give up now
The wheels of fortune circle back around
Future in the betting ring
A maze of outcomes drawn in golden string
And through this tangled thread
I see what's up ahead
A wild chase
A frantic pace
I've got to trust my luck and spin fate
Spin the roulette, see where it falls
Testing the limits and betting it all
Round and round, jumping into the circle
Over and over, a test of will
But the game is never easy
And the outcome is a mystery
But these are fates we're betting on
Caught alive
By flex and string
Casting lots together
At the start of everything
I'm not gonna give up yet
Wait for the days past
The time has come for fate to change at last
And if it's black or red, I'm moving up ahead
A perfect chance, in a starry dance
I spin this thread of fate with my own hands
I'm taking fate into my hands
Whoa yeah
After this tangled thread, I see what's up ahead
Hyper Jumpin' now
Hyper Jumpin'
作詞・作曲・編曲：PandaBoY
Lyrics, Composition & Arrangement: PandaBoY
Hyper Jumpin' now
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び出そう
Hyper Jumpin', let's leap out
Come on baby 輝いて
Come on baby, keep on shining
ハート キュンてパッてハッて
Heart beating fast and bright
Hyper Jumpin' 指の先まで
Hyper Jumpin', down to my fingertips
もっと もっと 刺激が欲しいの
I want even more, even more excitement
Hyper Jumpin' now
Hyper Jumpin'
子供っぽい はしゃぐ方がお得でしょ
Being childish and making a fuss is better, right?
Take it up 這い上がっていくテンション
Take it up, the tension is climbing
良い波 打ち返しまくるメンション
Replying back to all the good mentions
カオスを乗りこなして進むミッション
The mission is to ride through the chaos and move forward
このままスピード加速して
Accelerating the speed just like this
辿り着く先に 何があるんだろう
I wonder what's waiting at our destination
止まらない気持ちは助走つけて
Taking a running start with these unstoppable feelings
次元を超えて行こう さあ
Let's go beyond dimensions, come on
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び跳ねよう
Hyper Jumpin', let's jump around
ハイになってハイになるまで
Until we're high and fly higher,
Don't stop keep it up
Hyper Jumpin' 空の向こうまで
Hyper Jumpin', to the other side of the sky
もっと もっと 近づきたいの
I want to get closer, even closer
Whoa whoa
ドキドキしたい Gimme gimme gimme eye
I want to feel my heart throb, gimme gimme gimme eye
Whoa whoa
もっと もっと 高く跳びたいの
I want to jump higher, even higher
Hyper Jumpin' now
Hyper Jumpin'
斜めから 攻めて解答はQuestion
Attacking from an angle, the answer is a question
ネガティブを 切り裂いてくれる剣閃
A flash of a sword that slashes through the negative
流れるコメントと掛け合いセッション
A call-and-response session with the flowing comments
エイムを鍛えて狙い撃つフリクション
Sharpening my aim to shoot through the friction
This one no-no
キミならま・ま・ま
With you it's ma-ma-ma
邪魔するノイズは打ち消せバンバンバン
Cancel out the distracting noise, bang bang bang
遊びたいだけ 味わいつくして
I just want to play, enjoying it to the fullest
笑い飛ばして 蹴飛ばして
Laugh it off, kick it away,
Kicking Jump around jump around
このまま僕らは旅をして
We'll keep on traveling just like this
辿り着く先に 何があるんだろう
I wonder what's waiting at our destination
信じた未来とリンクして
Linking up with the future we believed in
次元を超えて行こう さあ
Let's go beyond dimensions, come on
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper Jumpin', let's jump across
ハイになってハイになるまで
Until we're high and fly higher,
Don't stop keep it up
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまで
Hyper Jumpin', to the other side of the sea
もっと もっと 近づきたいの
I want to get closer, even closer
Whoa whoa
ドキドキしたい Gimme gimme gimme eye
I want to feel my heart throb, gimme gimme gimme eye
Whoa whoa
もっと もっと 高く跳びたいの
I want to jump higher, even higher
Hyper Jumpin' now
目を覚ませ 目を凝らして
Wake up, open your eyes wide
Dramatic XViltration
作詞：Datenkou　作曲・編曲：Farhan Sarasin
Lyrics: Datenkou, Composition & Arrangement: Farhan Sarasin
夢から抜け出して
Break out from the dream
世界が今 呼吸する
The world is breathing now
我らの甦り
Our revival
鏡に映る
Reflected in the mirror
心に宿っている小さな光
A small light dwelling in the heart
さあ今も感じる
Come, I still feel it now
どこか心の奥で
Somewhere deep within my heart
呼び覚ました
It has awakened
忘れられない浮かぶメモリ
Unforgettable memories floating up
今の自分になるその前に
Before becoming who I am now
果てのない音色で迷い
Getting lost in endless timbres
そして黄昏が落ちて来る
And then twilight falls
どこまでも
Endlessly
引き締める鎖がまた
The chains tightening again
身体を止めていた
Were stopping my body
ためらいを覚えてしまって
Having learned hesitation
凍えて行くの
I'm freezing up
明日の向こう側には
On the other side of tomorrow
未知なるエリア
Is an unknown area
その境界線の先に待つのは
What waits beyond that boundary
一期のはじめ
The very beginning
未だ変わらず
Still unchanged
奈落の底へと落ちて行く
Falling down to the bottom of the abyss
知覚外知らぬ
Unknowing beyond perception
時計の針の音
The ticking of the clock's hands
記憶に残り
Remaining in memory
広がる海
The spreading sea
誰もがまだ知らない森の中に
Inside the forest that no one knows yet
宇宙を越え逃げ場所探して
Searching for a refuge beyond the universe
そんな過去もまだ頭に響いている
Such a past is still echoing in my head
解けない鎖を断ち
Cutting off the unbreakable chains
切れないままもがき
Struggling while unable to cut them
物語の始まり
The beginning of the story
探し続けたい
I want to keep searching
夢重力不可解な
Weightless gravity, mysterious
謎のようなことさ
Like a riddle
この身体の中で目覚めた
Awakened within this body
本当の姿
My true form
運命の
Fate's
カードが占う未来
Future predicted by the cards
真相は目の前
The truth is right before my eyes
解き放た鎖が消え
The released chains vanish
進めると信じて
Believing that I can move forward
新たな自分になって
Becoming a new self
光の方へ
Towards the light
遂に辿り着いた
Finally arrived
未知なるエリア
An unknown area
その境界線を越える日が来た
The day has come to cross that boundary
一期のはじめ
The very beginning
信じ合える仲間と一緒に
Together with friends who believe in each other
挑戦の狼煙をあげよう
Let's raise the signal fire of challenge
終わらない青春に
To the youth that never ends
理想が　追いつけ　頑張れ　落ちて
Let your ideals catch up, hang in there, and dive in!
青春　感じている　今　遊べ
I'm feeling my youth, so I'll play right now!
アチュー！
Achoo!
成長した姿を見せたい
I want to show how much I've grown
ビターな完璧　本番はもっと全力で
Bitter perfection, I'll give it my all for the real performance!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！フー！
Hi! Hi! Hi! Fu!
大切な思い出
Even though I have so many
たくさんあるけどね　まだ
Precious memories, there's still...
感傷に浸ってる暇はない
I have no time to be sentimental
今世紀最大級の夏が始まる
The greatest summer of this century is starting
想像の果てにある高み
The heights beyond our imagination
勝ち獲った景色は尊い
The scenery we've won is precious
逃げるな限界の壁越えて
Don't run away, overcome the wall of limits
僕らはまだチャレンジャー　イェーイ！
We are still challengers, yeah!
冷たい豪雨に溺れたって
Even if I drown in the cold downpour
確かな望みをたぐり寄せるように
I'll pull my certain hopes closer to me
期待外れだと誰かが嘆く
Someone laments that it wasn't what they expected
期待と痛いがいつも戦う
Expectations and pain are always at war
プライドだけを頼りに抗う　自分を信じたい
Resisting with only pride, I want to believe in myself
努力は報われる　笑いたい奴は笑ってろ
Effort will be rewarded, so let them laugh
感傷に浸ってる暇はない
I have no time to be sentimental
今世紀最大級の夏が始まる
The greatest summer of this century is starting
反響が足りない　もっともっと
The echoes aren't enough, more and more!
後悔はさせない
I won't let you have any regrets
想像の果てにある高み
The heights beyond our imagination
勝ち獲った景色は尊い
The scenery we've won is precious
逃げるな限界の壁越えて
Don't run away, overcome the wall of limits
僕らはまだチャレンジャー　イェーイ！
We are still challengers, yeah!
hololive production COUNTDOWN LIVE 2025▷2026
4th STAGE
夢見る空へ
Yumemiru Sora e
（ボーカル）
(Vocalizing)
重ねた手はギュッと離さずに
Don't ever let go of our joined hands
行くよ　行こう　夢見る空へ
Let's go, let's head to the dreaming sky
窓越しに見上げた
Looking up through the window
とても小さな空
At a very small sky
ここで出会えたのは
Meeting here was...
数えきれない奇跡
A countless series of miracles
繰り返した一歩が
The steps we've taken over and over
きらめきをつないで
Connected the sparkles together
星のような笑顔
A smile like a star
導いた
Led the way
Day by day
みんなの声が力になる
Everyone's voices give us strength
Step by step
ここでそれぞれ目指すもの
What each of us aims for here
それぞれ描くもの
What each of us draws
それぞれ願った夢
The dreams each of us wished for
重ねた手はギュッと離さずに
Don't ever let go of our joined hands
一人一人違う色で描き出すときめき
A fluttering heart drawn in each of our different colors
振り向くことなく真っすぐに
Heading straight without looking back
行くよ　行こう　夢見る空へ
Let's go, let's head to the dreaming sky
笑い合ったことや
The times we laughed together
尽きないわがまま
And our endless selfishness
思い出いっぱいなのに
Even though we have so many memories
夢見る空へ
不知火フレア/白銀ノエル/宝鐘マリン/兎田ぺこら
Yumemiru Sora e
Shiranui Flare / Shirogane Noel / Houshou Marine / Usada Pekora
あっと言う間の日々
In the blink of an eye, the days
上書きじゃなく受けて
Not overwriting, but receiving them
名前つけて保存
Giving them names and saving them
どれも全部大事って
That every single one is important—
言いきれる
I can say that for sure
One for...
みんなの溜めが力になる
Everyone's gathering becomes strength
All for...
今日は賑やかすぎるくらい
Today is so lively
笑顔がもう止まらない
I can't stop smiling
思いは膨らんでいく
The feelings keep growing
重ねた
The moments we've layered...
今
...this moment...
ぎゅっと
...I tightly...
噛み締めた
...savor it
一人ひとり違う声で歌う空広がる
Spreading across the sky, each of us singing with a different voice
風も感じたら
If you feel the wind
真っ直ぐに
Head straight on
行くよ
Let's go
行こうよ夢見る空へ
Let's go to the dream-filled sky
憧れ手伸ばし
Reaching out towards my dream
掴み取ったその光が
The light I've grasped
いつの日か
One day
また誰かの憧れに変わる
It will become someone else's dream
つなぎよ
Connect it all
重ねた手はぎゅっと離さずに
Holding our layered hands tightly, never letting go
一人ひとり違う色で描き出すときめき
Creating excitement, each in our own different colors
出会った全てにありがとう
Thank you for everything we've encountered
奇跡だって起こし続けずっとずっとそばにいるよ
Continuing to make miracles happen, I'll be by your side forever and ever
行くよ
Let's go
行こうよ夢見る空へ
Let's go to the dream-filled sky
ホロライブゲーマーズ！
Hololive Gamers!
We are GAMERS!!!!
戌神ころね/猫又おかゆ/大神ミオ/白上フブキ
Inugami Korone / Nekomata Okayu / Ookami Mio / Shirakami Fubuki
ホロライブの狐だぞー！
I'm the Hololive fox!
みんなお待たせ！
Thanks for waiting, everyone!
We are GAMERS!!!!
楽しむ準備はできてるよね！
You're ready to have fun, right!
せーの！
Ready, set!
We are GAMERS!!!!
こんこん！
Kon kon!
狐が参上
The fox has arrived
白上・ケモ耳・白髪フブキ
Shirakami, animal ears, white-haired Fubuki
突っ込んでちゃ始まらない
It won't start if you keep retorting
君はすこん部に入部しなさい
You must join the Sukon-bu
（はい！イェー！ はい！イェー！）
(Hai! Yeah! Hai! Yeah!)
こんこん絶好調頂戴
Kon kon, give me your best condition
オタクじゃないし得意はMC
I'm not an otaku, and my specialty is MCing
赤くないしやる気特盛おいしい
I'm not red, but my motivation is extra large and delicious
ミオしゃん！
Mio-shan!
うち、うち、うちだよ！
It's me, me, it's me!
大神ミオだよ
It's Ookami Mio
黒髪・ケモ耳・大神ミオ
Black hair, animal ears, Ookami Mio
ミオーン！
Mio-n!
突っ込んで止めます
I'll stop it with a retort
ウチらママ笑い出すと止まらない
Once we start laughing like moms, we can't stop
ゲラゲラ
Gera gera
つまり実はポンコツ？
So, actually a klutz?
占いステップしちゃおっと
Let's do the fortune-telling step
タロット占いで見る未来
The future seen through tarot readings
ホラゲーはやりたくない！
I don't want to play horror games!
4人揃えばゲーマーズ最強
When the four of us are together, Gamers are the strongest
君も朝晩ハピタス
You too, morning and night, be happy
クリアを目指してレベル上げ
Aiming for the clear, raising levels
今日は何プレイしよう？
What should we play today?
君のハートもコーデしちゃう
I'll even coordinate your heart
選択をしてシミュレーション
Make a choice and simulate
初見も古参も大歓迎
First-timers and veterans are all welcome
さあ、ゲームは楽しみね
Come on, games are fun, right
G-A-M-E-R-S
We are GAMERS!!!!
おかゆ！
Okayu!
もぐもぐ猫又おかゆ
Mogu mogu, Nekomata Okayu
おにぎりおにぎり はいどうぞ
Onigiri, onigiri, here you go
キラキラふらふら 性分 猫だもん
Sparkling, wandering, that's just my nature, I'm a cat after all
ほら、僕でよくない？
See, wouldn't I be good enough?
まったりゆっくり跳ねるリズム
A chill, slow, bouncing rhythm
全肯定するおかゆイズム
Full affirmation, Okayu-ism
全肯定コーリズムOK
Full affirmation, ice-rhythm OK
毎日僕と一緒に
Every day together with me
ころね！
Korone!
おはよー！ゆびゆびー！
Ohayou! Yubi yubi-!
パンは捏ね捏ね 戌神ころね
Kneading bread, Inugami Korone
キャバリア・キング・チャールズ・スパニエルって噛まずに言えるかな？
Cavalier King Charles Spaniel, can you say it without biting your tongue?
なまりイントネーション 割れるリアクション
Dialect intonation, breaking reactions
まずは指を捧げてくれる？（ハイ！師匠！）
First, will you offer me your fingers? (Yes! Master!)
わかった、メッセージ超OK
Understood, message super OK
好物のレバ刺しをお届け
Delivering my favorite, beef liver sashimi
世にうそぶけば
If I feign indifference to the world
ゲームは最高
Games are the best
フラグ立てれば
If I set a flag
即回収
Immediate collection
エイム鍛えて
Honing my aim
狙い撃ち
Sniping them down
今日は
Today
なにプレイしよ？
What should I play?
君のハートも
Even your heart
回復しちゃう
I'll end up healing
ワクワクするぜ
I'm getting excited
この感情
This feeling
大逆転が
A major comeback
やめられない
I can't stop
だって
Because
ゲームが好きなんだもん
I just love games so much
突然ですが、ボーナスチャレンジの時間です！
Suddenly, it's time for the Bonus Challenge!
大きな声でレスポンスして、高得点を狙いましょう！
Let's aim for a high score by responding in a loud voice!
Are you ready?
せーの、コンコン！
Ready, Kon kon!
コンコン！
Kon kon!
せーの、ミョーンミョーン！
Ready, Myon myon!
ミョーンミョーン！
Myon myon!
せーの、もぐもぐ！
Ready, Mogu mogu!
もぐもぐ！
Mogu mogu!
せーの、ゆびゆび！
Ready, Yubi yubi!
ゆびゆび！
Yubi yubi!
せーの、コンコン！
Ready, Kon kon!
コンコン！
Kon kon!
せーの、ミョーンミョーン！
Ready, Myon myon!
ミョーンミョーン！
Myon myon!
せーの、もぐもぐ！
Ready, Mogu mogu!
もぐもぐ！
Mogu mogu!
せーの、ゆびゆび！
Ready, Yubi yubi!
ゆびゆび！
Yubi yubi!
ほい！
Hoi!
世にうそぶけば
If I feign indifference to the world
ゲームは最高
Games are the best
うまくいかなくても
Even if things don't go well
コンティニュー
Continue
エンドロールまで
Until the end credits
あきらめない
I won't give up
エンディングを見に行こう
Let's go see the ending
君のハートも攻略しちゃう
I'll even conquer your heart
選択をしてシミュレーション
Make a choice and simulate
助けも強さもダイアログ
Help and strength are both in the dialogue
やっぱゲームは楽しいね
After all, games are fun, right?
WE ARE GAMERS!
こうして2025年の幕が閉じるのであった。
And thus, the curtain closed on the year 2025.
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make our newborn heart-throbs resound
最高の時間 最高の仲間と
The best of times with the best of friends
きらめきに乗って
Riding on the sparkle
YAY!
キラメキライダー☆
Kira-Kira Rider☆
覚えてるかな 最初の歌
I wonder if you remember our first song
懐かしいね
It brings back memories
私 声が震えていた
My voice was trembling back then
眩しかった
It was so dazzling
あの日から続く未来は
The future continuing from that day
みんなと掴んだ今日だよ
Is the today we grasped together
もっと もっと もっと もっと
More, more, more, more
加速するハート
Our accelerating hearts
一緒に行こうよ
Let's go together
どこまでも
Wherever we may go
I ready?
Are you ready?
準備はOK
The preparation is OK
開け 夢の扉を
Open the door to dreams
1, 2, 3 きらめきライダー
1, 2, 3, Kira-Kira Rider
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make our newborn heart-throbs resound
最高の時間 最高の仲間と
The best of times with the best of friends
ここにいるよ 見つけてくれたから
I'm right here because you found me
君に会いたくてやってきたんだ
I came here because I wanted to meet you
みんなで歌おう
Let's all sing together
終わらないメロディ
The melody that never ends
きらめきに乗って
Riding on the sparkle
届いてるかな 私の声
I wonder if my voice is reaching you
はっきりと
Loud and clear
届けたいのは 君に笑顔
What I want to deliver is a smile to you
そのスマイル
That smile
理想の交差に 悔しくて
Regretting the intersection of ideals
みんなと泣き笑ったね
We cried and laughed together, didn't we?
ぎゅっと ぎゅっと ぎゅっと ぎゅっと
Tightly, tightly, tightly, tightly
すべて抱きしめて
Embracing everything
一緒に行こうよ
Let's go together
どこまでも
Wherever we may go
I ready?
Are you ready?
準備はOK
The preparation is OK
進め 自分の道を
Move forward on your own path
1, 2, 3 きらめきライダー
1, 2, 3, Kira-Kira Rider
好きな気持ち カラフルに奏でたいな
I want to play my feelings of love colorfully
最高の場所 最高の仲間と
The best of places with the best of friends
ここにいるよ 幻なんかじゃない
I'm right here, it's not some illusion
ジャンプ！
Jump!
君の心が幸せに染まるように
So that your heart will be colored with happiness
重ねていくハーモニー
Layers of harmony we build
煌めき纏って
Draped in sparkling brilliance
歌い続けたいな
I want to keep on singing
踊り続けたいな
I want to keep on dancing
そんな願いはわがままでもいいでしょう
A wish like that can be selfish, can't it?
だって楽しすぎて止まらない
Because it's just too much fun to stop
輝くステージでもっともっと
On this shining stage, even more, even more
おいでよ！
Come join us!
ずっと！
Always!
嬉しい楽しい愛しいだけじゃ語れない
Being happy, having fun, or loving isn't enough to describe it
今も今も悩みはあるけど
Even now, even now, I still have worries, but...
ここにいるよ私
I'm right here
ここにいるよ
君と同じ世界を
Gazing at the same world
見つめて
As you
行くよ！ キラメキライダー！
Let's go! Kirameki Rider!
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make this fresh excitement resonate
最高の時間 最高の仲間と
The best of times, with the best of friends
ここにいるよ見つけてくれたから
I'm here because you found me
君に会いたくてやってきたんだ
I came here because I wanted to see you
みんなで歌おう
Let's all sing together
終わらないメロディ
To this never-ending melody
煌めきにのって
Riding on the sparkle
煌めき纏って
Draped in sparkling brilliance
イェーイ！
Yeah!
2025年もあと少し！ みんな盛り上がってる？
2025 is almost over! Is everyone hyped up?
今回はカウントダウンライブ！
This time it's a countdown live!
あれ？ あれれ？ コメントの熱量、なんだか少なくない？
Huh? Hmm? Isn't the comment enthusiasm a bit low?
まだまだ足りない！ こんなんじゃ！
It's still not enough! Not like this!
いっくよー！
Here we go!
この！この！この！この！
This! This! This! This!
浮気は許しません！
I won't allow any cheating!
私だけに尽くしてね！
Devote yourself only to me!
私だけにヒット（集中）し、尽くさなきゃ嫌だあ、絶対ぞ！
Focus only on me, you have to serve me, or I'll hate it, definitely!
ズンチャ！
Zuncha!
カモンカモン　チョチョチョ　誰も
Come on, come on, cho cho cho, don't let anyone...
よそ見をしたら　ポンポンポンメッ！
...look away, or I'll punish you! Bad!
メロメロめらっぽ　プププくらん
Melo-melo melappo, pu-pu-pu klan
ぴゅあおししましょう　アップププ
Let's do a pure oshi, ap-pu-pu-pu
ずっと歌を　見逃さないでしょう？
You won't miss a single song, will you?
目移りはダメ　本当イヤイヤ
No looking at others, I really hate that
いつも見て見て　ウォッチも合ってる？
Look at me always, are our eyes meeting?
あなたが推してくれる愛情の桁
The sheer scale of the love you give me
私は捧げる　栄養を　さあ！
I'll give you nourishment, come on!
Love Love Love　後ろ指チュムチュム
Love Love Love, kiss the finger pointed at my back
とってもとってもとってもとっても　愛して欲しい
I want you to love me very, very, very, very much
ハピハピハピ　最上級ハギュハギュ
Happy happy happy, the ultimate hug-hug
おはよおはよおはよ　はっきりはっきりはっきりはっきり
Good morning, good morning, clearly, clearly, clearly, clearly
ここらへんでしょ　ピコピコ気持ちの
It's around here, isn't it? My piko-piko feelings...
バロメーターが　超上がる
...barometer is rising like crazy!
ぴゅあおし！ ぴゅあおし！ ぴゅあおし！
Pure oshi! Pure oshi! Pure oshi!
もう本当に本当に本当に　わかってね
Really, really, really, please understand
わかってね
Please understand
おーいみんな！ ここまでついてこれてる？
Hey everyone! Can you keep up with us so far?
この後もこの調子でいくよ！
Let's keep going like this!
うりゃおい！ うりゃおい！
Urya oi! Urya oi!
ちょっと待ってなんで他の子　褒めるの？
Wait a second, why are you praising other girls?
よそ見は　プツプツプッ！
No looking away! Snap, snap, snap!
私が今　気になってるでしょ？
I'm the one you're interested in right now, right?
ありえないの　ありえない
It's unbelievable, unbelievable
プンプン　他の子に　チュチュチュだけ
Pouting, just giving kisses to other girls...
よそ見したよね？　うそマジ無理で
You looked away, didn't you? No way, I seriously can't
ぴゅあおし死んじゃう　私おこんじゃう
My pure oshi will die, I'm gonna get mad
指切りしてよ　針千本
Pinky swear with me, or swallow a thousand needles
心変わりしたら本当に
If you have a change of heart, I'll really...
拗ねる　怒る　泣いちゃうからね！
...pout, get angry, and cry!
ズンチャ！
Zuncha!
ぴゅあおし　してないね？
You aren't doing a pure oshi, are you?
私だけに　尽くして
Devote yourself only to me
る（るー）
-ing!
ダメほらコメントが愛に溢れている
No, look, the comments are overflowing with love
必死のHP　みるみる回復
My critical HP is recovering instantly
したよ満ち満ちなパワーじゃん
Look, I'm full of power now!
ごめごめごめ　ちょごめごめごめ
Sorry, sorry, sorry, a little sorry, sorry, sorry
Love Love Love　後ろ指チュムチュム
Love Love Love, kiss the finger pointed at my back
いっぱいっぱいっぱいっぱい　愛して欲しい
I want you to love me so much, so much, so much
ハピハピハピ　最上級ハギュハギュ
Happy happy happy, the ultimate hug-hug
うっとりうっとりうっとり
Entranced, entranced, entranced
コリコリコリコリ...
Kori-kori-kori-kori...
私のため日々お仕事励んでくれてありがとう
Thank you for working hard every day for my sake
推しも推しも愛おしい
Both my oshi and your oshi are so precious
絶対絶対絶対絶対絶対絶対絶対絶対いっぱい
Absolutely, absolutely, absolutely, absolutely, so many times
お願いね
Please, okay?
このこのこのこの
This girl, this girl, this girl, this girl
うー、このこのこのこの
Ooh, this girl, this girl, this girl, this girl
このこのこのこのこのー！
This girl, this girl, this girl, this girl, this girl!
銀河の果てまで推してほしい
I want you to support me to the ends of the galaxy
同じ未来を見ていたい あの夢手にしたい
I want to see the same future, I want to grasp that dream
それぞれ違った 心で走れよ
Run forward with our individual hearts!
どこを見ても真っ暗な場所に芽生えてた
It sprouted in a place where everything was pitch black
ほんの小さな希望に この瞳奪われた
My eyes were captivated by a tiny glimmer of hope
不安で揺れる心を上手くチューニングして
Successfully tuning my heart that wavered with anxiety
ほんの小さな勇気を 握りしめていたよ
I was clutching onto a tiny bit of courage
諦めの文字 手放して進む
Letting go of the word "surrender" and moving forward
苦しい時も もう私は一人じゃないから
Because even in painful times, I'm not alone anymore
だからこそ夢追いかけたい ワクワク止まらない
That's why I want to chase my dreams, the excitement won't stop
想像を超えてく 世界見せてあげる
I'll show you a world that exceeds your imagination
アクセスしてみてみたい 後悔なんてそうさせない
I want to try accessing it, I won't let you have any regrets
それぞれ違った 心で走れよ
Run forward with our individual hearts!
夜空に輝く眩しい思いは
The dazzling feelings shining in the night sky
見たこともない光を リアルに届けるよ
Will deliver a light you've never seen before to reality
いつも聞こえるエールをここにキャプチャーして
Capturing the cheers I always hear right here
また新しい光を 探したくなるよ
It makes me want to look for a new light again
君の笑顔は 誇らしく進む
Your smile moves forward proudly
悲しい時に 見返すよ力湧くから
When I'm sad, I'll look back at it, because it gives me strength
胸を張って夢追いかけたい 奇跡のストーリー
I want to puff out my chest and chase my dreams, a miraculous story
一緒に作ろう 終わらない夢を
Let's create an endless dream together
誰一人欠かせない 相まったこの世界
In this world where everyone is indispensable and intertwined
それぞれ違った 心で彩れ
Color it with our individual hearts!
悲しい時も
Even when it's sad
寂しい時も
Even when it's lonely
信じ合えるものがある
There's something we can believe in together
密かにこの鼓動 鳴らし続けたい
Deep down, I want to keep this heartbeat sounding
モノクロの世界に 溢れ出すよ笑顔たち
Smiles will overflow into this monochrome world
憧れの舞台立ちたい まぶしく輝きたい
I want to stand on the stage I've longed for, I want to shine dazzlingly
時になみだして また笑い合いたい
Sometimes we'll cry, but I want us to laugh together again
同じ未来を見ていたい あの夢手にしたい
I want to see the same future, I want to grasp that dream
踏み出そう 奇跡の一歩を
Let's take a step, a miraculous step
息切らして夢追いかけたい ワクワク止まらない
Running out of breath, I want to chase my dreams, the excitement won't stop
想像を超えてく 世界見せてあげる
I'll show you a world that exceeds your imagination
アクセスしてみてみない？ 後悔なんてここにはない
Won't you try accessing it? There are no regrets here
それぞれ違った 心で作るよ
We'll create it with our individual hearts!
みんな、コークは持ったかな？
Everyone, got your Cokes?
持ちましたー！
Got them!
乾杯するー！
Let's toast!
こら、こら、早いよ、ラプちゃん。
Hey, hey, too early, Lapu-chan.
避けるな、当たる！
Don't dodge, it'll hit!
年越しのタイミングでみんなで
「乾杯」ってするんだよ。
We're all going to say "Cheers"
at the turn of the year.
やだやだ、もう喉カラカラ。
No, no, my throat is already parched.
楽しみだね。
I'm so excited.
ね、みこさん？
Right, Miko-san?
みこさん？
Miko-san?
いやー、いいライブだったね。
Wow, that was a great live.
お疲れ。
Good job.
この後どうする？
What should we do after this?
ご飯食べる？
Grab some food?
いやー、どこも混んでんじゃない？
Well, won't everywhere be crowded?
確かに。お腹空きましたね。
True. I'm hungry.
あ、運転手さん、まっすぐね。
Ah, driver, go straight.
おう、おう。
Yeah, yeah.
おい、お前ら！
Hey, you guys!
何帰ってんだ！
Why are you heading back!
乾杯！乾杯！
Cheers! Cheers!
フブちゃんたちがついてきてる。
Fubu-chan and the others are following us.
おらおらフブ様寂しくなっちゃったのかね。
My, my, did Fubu-sama get lonely?
なんか怒ってない？
Aren't they looking a bit angry?
あ、やばい。あのイタズラがバレたかな？
Ah, oh no. Did they find out about that prank?
あはは、やりすぎたんですかね。
Ahaha, did we go too far?
やばいかも。
Might be bad.
運転手さん、ごめん！
Driver, sorry!
みこのドラテクで逃げるぞ！
I'll escape with my driving techniques!
わー、わー！
Whoa, whoa!
あ、来た。
Ah, here they come.
すごいすごい。
Amazing, amazing.
フブちゃんごめんて、もうイタズラしないから。
Fubu-chan, sorry, I won't play pranks anymore.
ダメだよみこみこ、反省しなさい。
That's no good, Miko-miko. Reflect on yourself.
あんたも共犯だもんな！
You're an accomplice too!
何の話だよ。
What are you talking about?
二人ともこれ持って。
You two, hold this.
何するの？
What are we doing?
もうすぐ新年だよ！
It's almost the New Year!
おー！
Oh!
乾杯！
Cheers!
HAPPY NEW YEAR!
明けましておめでとう！
Happy New Year!
今年もよろしくね。
Let's have a great year together.
今年もいっぱい…
This year too, lots of...
そういえば、イタズラってなんなの？
By the way, what was that prank?
あ、それね。
Ah, that.
フブさんのヘソ、冷やしたんだよ。
We chilled Fubu-san's belly button.
恐怖！
The horror!
この後は、コカ・コーラと一緒に
スペシャルライブステージ！
After this, a special live stage
with Coca-Cola!
イエーイ！
Yay!
SPECIAL STAGE
そうさ　ずっと　僕らの軌跡が
That's right, our trajectory will always...
途切れないように歌うんだ
...continue as we sing.
もっと　高く　大きな声で
Louder and higher with our voices.
Prism Melody
聞こえてた　何かが　始まるサイン
I heard it, the sign that something is starting.
集まって　気づけば　鼓動を奏でた
We gathered and realized we're playing a heartbeat.
夢に見る　だけじゃもう　足りないでしょう？
Just dreaming isn't enough anymore, is it?
君を待ってる　世界があるよ
There's a world out there waiting for you.
楽しい予感にほら　飛び乗っちゃえばいい
Just jump onto that fun premonition.
ときめきは止められないから
Because this excitement cannot be stopped.
運ぼう　連れて行くよ　光の真ん中
Let's go, I'll take you to the center of the light.
夢の先へ
Beyond our dreams.
羽ばたける　勇気は君の願い
The courage to fly is your wish.
みんなで　繋いだ　この軌跡が
This trajectory we've connected together...
途切れないように歌うんだ
...will continue as we sing.
もっと　高く　大きな声で
Louder and higher with our voices.
答えとか　理屈に　惑わされて
Don't be led astray by answers or logic.
彷徨っても　戻って　これる場所があったんだ
Even if we wander, there's a place we can return to.
自分なり　道行く　僕らも旅
We're on a journey, going our own way.
願いだけが　道標だよ
Our wishes are our guideposts.
夢の色が変わっても　変わらないメロディ
Even if the color of dreams changes,
the melody remains the same.
君のために　僕らのために
For you, and for us.
歌おう　そうさきっと　僕らの軌跡は
Let's sing, our trajectory will surely...
終わらないよ
...never end.
涙さえ　きっかけに変えていこう
Let's turn even our tears into a new beginning.
信じて　くれる　仲間と一緒に
With the friends who believe in us...
どこへだって　飛び出して行こう
...we can go anywhere.
もっと　遠く　空へ
Further and further into the sky.
大きな声で
With a loud voice
僕らの未来へと
Towards our future
いくよ！
Let's go!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
未来の僕らに まだ見ぬ君に
To our future selves, and to you we've yet to meet
伝えたいこと たくさんあるんだ
There's so much I want to tell you
分かち合いたい 今は当たり前なんかじゃない
This moment we want to share is not something to be taken for granted
翼を広げ さあ今 飛ぼう
Spread your wings, let's fly now
Take my heart 連れていくよ
Take my heart, I'll take you there
光の真ん中 夢の先へ
To the center of the light, beyond the dreams
羽ばたける 勇気は君の願い
The courage to take flight is your wish
みんなで 繋いでいこう
Let's all connect it together
この奇跡が 途切れないように歌うんだ
I'll sing so that this miracle won't end
もっと高く 大きな声で
Higher and with a louder voice
僕らの未来へと どこまでも響け
Let it echo forever towards our future
Prism Melody
Show Them (Who You Are)
Won't you just forget about the past
'Cause in time it will never matter
But the love we had I'm hoping it will last
Bersamamu t'lah lewati
Having gone through it with you
Tawa dan canda jadi memori
Laughter and jokes become memories
Pastikan harinya kan cerah
Make sure the day will be bright
Guna menggapai mimpi
To reach for the dream
Through the winds we're meant to do
For it's time to make it true
Together we can always stand
Your hand in my hand
Forever hand in hand
Genggamlah mimpi yang kau layangkan
Hold onto the dream you've flown
Cari daratan
Look for land
Lalala... tak kan sendiri
Lalala... you won't be alone
It's time to show them who you are
Just shout it from the mountain high
To the sky we go, we go
Bersamamu t'lah lewati
Having gone through it with you
Tawa dan canda jadi memori
Laughter and jokes become memories
Pastikan harinya kan cerah
Make sure the day will be bright
Guna menggapai mimpi
To reach for the dream
Cerah kan mimpimu nanti
Will brighten your dreams later
Through the winds we're meant to do
For it's time to make it true
Together we can always stand
Your hand in my hand
Forever hand in hand
Genggamlah mimpi yang kau layangkan
Hold onto the dream you've flown
Cari daratan
Look for land
Lalala... tak kan sendiri
Lalala... you won't be alone
Show them who you are
Fly so far, fly and show them who you are
Always singing lalala...
Be who you're meant to be
頑張れ！
Do your best!
...show them and travel far
Running and show them who you are
Keindahan dunia akhirnya
The beauty of the world at last
Semua kan baik saja
Everything will be alright
Arahkan pandanganmu
Direct your gaze
Tajam lurus ke depan
Sharp straight ahead
Tuk mulai bermimpi
To start dreaming
Genggamlah yang kau cari
Hold on to what you search for
Takkan ada...
There won't be...
La la la la la...
Kau takkan sendiri
You won't be alone
Show them and travel far
Running and show them who you are
I'll be singing...
La la la la la...
Kau takkan pernah sendiri
You'll never be alone
It's time to show them who you are
Just shout it from the mountain high
To the sky we go...
We go, oh!
All for One
作詞：Steph 作曲：BLACCHOLE / Haruna / Yohei Abe
編曲：BLACCHOLE
All for One
Lyrics: Steph Composition: BLACCHOLE / Haruna / Yohei Abe
Arrangement: BLACCHOLE
Just look around and see
It's so incredible
So many smiles in the sea of light
Take one step with me
And you'll be dazzled
There's magic in the air tonight
The hours zoom zoom zoom
My heart goes boom boom boom
The world is brighter because you believe in me
Let's shout it loud loud loud
Our time is right now
We're on the edge of destiny
For a moment I can dream with you
Every miracle we hope for might come true
We come together reaching out from far and wide
And suddenly you're here by my side
When our voices and hearts unite
We're gonna shine bright together, we're all for one
Let's sing! All for one
The thrill of happiness is all around us
Jump in 'cause it's all for one
Let's sing! All for one
We're on our way to good times, goodbye
We'll treasure this day the rest of our lives
Hey! All that we waited for
The dream we're striving toward
We're singing all for one, all for one
Everything's in motion
Get up, it's a celebration
Come see the wonders here beyond imagination
We're joining hands for the world to see
Uh-huh, feel the love and the energy
The hours zoom zoom zoom
My heart goes boom boom boom
A hazy whirlwind of dreams and reality
Let's shout it loud loud loud
Our time is right now
We're here together, finally
Every moment takes my breath away
There's a feeling here that words cannot convey
Hear the rhythm as we rise to meet the song
And suddenly our hearts beat as one
Every voice ringing loud and clear
So glad to be here together, we're all for one
Let's sing! All for one
We'll sing in harmony and we'll be happy
Jump in 'cause it's all for one
Let's sing! All for one
Keep up the hype, it's good times, goodbye
Remember this night the rest of our lives
Hey! Raise up your hands and sway
Your light will lead our way
We're shining all for one, all for one
Stamping our memories, our joy, and our hope
We'll gather and we'll sing upon this endless road, oh-oh
Feel the music in your passion, it's ours
We're with you right now, so let the good times roll, oh-oh
Every time that I'm with you
I could swear it's like a wish is coming true
So I believe in you if you believe in me
Together we can chase all our dreams
One, two, three, four, five!
When our voices and hearts unite
We're gonna shine bright together, we're all for one
Let's sing! All for one
The thrill of happiness is all around us
Jump in 'cause it's all for one
Let's sing! All for one
We're on our way to good times, goodbye
We'll treasure this day the rest of our lives
Hey! All that we waited for
The dream we're striving toward
We're singing all for one, all for one
皆さん、あけましておめでとうございます！
あけおめー！
Happy New Year, everyone!
Happy New Year!
Reach to the top! We are... ReGLOSS!
ここからはホロライブデバイス、コラボステージです。
聴いてください、FG ROADSTER by ReGLOSS！
From here on is the hololive DEV_IS collab stage.
Please listen to FG ROADSTER by ReGLOSS!
Let's go!
搭載V8エンジン　第7感持ってる原人
Equipped with a V8 engine, primitive man with a 7th sense
ロックするこの世界と全人類
この5人でゲームをゲームチェンジ
Locking this world and all humanity
With these five, we change the game
唸る4輪発車前　皆さんサンキュー散乱火
The groaning four wheels before departure, thank you everyone, scattered fire
対する2体の担当は　獲る1番ここからずら
The two opposite parties in charge, taking first place, move aside
Hey!
幾分か超えて頂点
Crossing the peak somewhat
チャンスも全土だ同然
Chances are throughout the land
昇り上げる超点
Climbing to the extreme point
サブトントンで絶好調
Sub-ton-ton and in top form
乗り込め FG ROADSTER
Get in, FG ROADSTER
特殊部隊集合　能力者
Special forces assemble, ability users
この歴史なほら超豪華
Look at this history, it's super luxurious
ぶっちぎりでおきざり強奪
Leaving them in the dust, a robbery
今高速でぶち抜いていく大気圏
Now breaking through the atmosphere at high speed
エンジンからジェットの炎揺れている開基線
Jet flames from the engine, a swaying base line
閃光広がる大地を越えていく回帰線
Crossing the land where flashes spread, a tropic line
バックミラーにビッグブルーが映ってる IB My Year
Big Blue reflected in the rearview mirror, IB My Year
打ち上げたいから飛んでくうち、羅刹だ
Since I want to launch, I'm a Rakshasa while flying
この年内くち果てないです
This year won't end
銀河に印し　旅人
Marking the galaxy, a traveler
見えてるでっかいビジョン
I can see the big vision
燃えてるメンバー一同
All members are burning
ただ今現在　進行形
Right now, in the present progressive
超えていく世界、希望
Crossing worlds, hope
殻破り one step
Breaking the shell, one step
心臓が monster
The heart is a monster
エリアス足りな
Not enough areas
FG Partyな
An FG party
光る this monster
Shining this monster
Heavy booster
目覚めていく本能は
The awakening instinct is
蒼い炎を
The blue flame
VFS Let's go
溶け出すなかゼロから
While melting from zero
空まで　永遠まで
To the sky, to eternity
走る FG ROADSTER
Running FG ROADSTER
唸るブースター
The roaring booster
路の果て見せて
Show me the end of the road
今ジェネシス見せて
Now show me Genesis
あけましておめでとうございます！
Happy New Year!
ここからは私たちFLOWGLOWが
ReGLOSS先輩の「Feeling Gradation」をかまさせていただきます！
From here on, we, FLOWGLOW, will be performing
ReGLOSS-senpais' "Feeling Gradation"!
ニコたんが来た。
Nico-tan is here.
セクシーに行くぞ、しょっぴしょま。
Let's be sexy, shoppi-shoma.
エンジで快、レッツゴー！頑張るぞ。
Engine ready, let's go! I'll do my best.
皆さん、ピカピカな... うん、ビビー！
Everyone, sparkly... Uh, Bibee!
私の歌に、おいで。
Come into my song.
VIBE... 激しく響くビート
VIBE... The heavily echoing beat
紐解いたスピリチュアル
Unraveled spiritual
様変わりしてショータイム
A complete change, it's showtime
全然悪くないイマジネーション
Not bad at all, imagination
期待の麒麟は腹這わって
The anticipated Qilin is lying low
悲しみには別れを告げ
Saying farewell to sadness
酸いも甘いも　中に放り出して
Tossing both the sour and the sweet inside
滲む空ピンクはバラ色
The blurry pink sky is rose-colored
どれだけうまく見せようとしても
No matter how well you try to show it
君がいなければ　何の味もない
Without you, it has no flavor
かすり傷すらつかない幻想
An illusion that doesn't even leave a scratch
針の落ちないレコードさ
Like a record with no needle dropping
高い熱度で色づいて
Colored by intense heat
風を背にして
With the wind at my back
Come let's run
外へと吹き荒れる
Blowing wildly outward
向かい風にも心
Even in the headwind, my heart
靡かせて
Letting it flutter
飛び出せ to the future
Leap out to the future
ライン際だって　荒らしにしか見えない
Even on the edge, it only looks like a storm
ときめいてしまえば
If you feel the excitement
瞬く間に広がる開放
Release spreading in the blink of an eye
一つ一つ全てがドラマ
Each and every thing is a drama
街は見た DEV_IS The Light
The city saw DEV_IS The Light
変わる変わる色づくパノラマ
The changing, changing colored panorama
満ち溢れる フィーリンググラデーション
Overflowing Feeling Gradation
飛び出せ you make me high
Leap out, you make me high
恐れるものはない The Light
There is nothing to fear, The Light
綺麗ださ夜明けが
The dawn is beautiful
どんな明日も照らすよ
It will illuminate any tomorrow
Ah...
Mr. The Light, Hey!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
最後の曲は...
The last song is...
Our Bright Parade!
イエーイ！
Yay!
パレード、パレード、パレード
Parade, parade, parade
輝くんだよ
I'm going to shine
呼び合う声を合図に
With calling voices as the signal
パレパレパレ
Parade, parade, parade
探しに行く
We go to find it
スカートはラウンドだって
Our skirts go round and round
まだ 独り言 続いた
My monologue still continued
ただ 始めたくて 走った
I ran, just wanting to start
遠く 暗がりに 灯った
A light in the distant darkness
それは 眩しすぎた 名前
It was a name far too bright
それは 優しすぎる 思い出
They are memories far too kind
もっと 近づけと 手を伸ばした
I reached out to get closer
思いがけず 結び合った
We unexpectedly joined hands
ほら 今 迷い子は 僕らになった
Look, now the lost children have become us
パレパレパレ 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade, let's shine
悔しさも 愛しさも 全て おいで
Regrets and affection, bring them all along
風 夢 羽 飛び立てるさ
With wind, dreams, and wings, we can take flight
ささやかな 祝いの光
A small light of celebration
終わりなき 日差し
Endless sunlight
君を見つけたこと 胸を張れるよ
Finding you is something I can be proud of
ここから これから Our Bright Parade
From here, from now on, Our Bright Parade
まだ 頼りない 横顔
Still an uncertain profile
歌を 恥ずかしくって 泣いた
I cried because I was embarrassed to sing
誰も 解けない 暇に
In a time that no one can unravel
いつか また 会える おまじない
A lucky charm to meet again someday
あの日 手のひらに 始まった ストーリー
A story that began in our palms that day
数えきれない 言の葉
Countless words
数えるような 思いじゃないさ
They aren't feelings you can just count
ほら 今 僕らを ひとつと 呼ぼう
Look, now let's call us one
パレパレパレ 美しいんだよ
Parade, parade, parade, it's beautiful
許し合える 切ない夜は 煌めく
Painful nights when we forgive each other sparkle
雨 晴れ カレ 待ってた空
Rain, sun, the sky we were waiting for
相応しい 旅路とは
What makes a worthy journey
君と歩くことさ
Is walking with you
君と歩くことなんだ
「ただいま」を聞けば
If I hear "I'm home"
「おかえり」って 叫ぶよ
I'll shout "Welcome back!"
当たり前じゃないか
Isn't that obvious?
パレパレパレ 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade, let's shine
暗がりを 満たすのは 君だ 僕だ
The ones filling the darkness are you and me
パレパレパレ 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade, let's shine
悔しさも 愛しさも 全て おいで
Regrets and affection, bring them all along
風 夢 羽 飛び立てるさ
With wind, dreams, and wings, we can take flight
ささやかな 祝いの光
A small light of celebration
終わりなき 日差し
Endless sunlight
君と飛び込んだよ
I jumped in with you
素敵な スタートさ
It's a wonderful start
ここから これから Our Bright Parade
From here, from now on, Our Bright Parade
Our Bright Parade
キャスト
Cast
ときのそら / ロボ子さん / AZKi / さくらみこ
Tokino Sora / Roboco-san / AZKi / Sakura Miko
アキ・ローゼンタール / 赤井はあと / 白上フブキ
Aki Rosenthal / Akai Haato / Shirakami Fubuki
セットリスト
Setlist
「FG ROADSTER」
"FG ROADSTER"
「RENEGADE」
"RENEGADE"
「アワータイムイエロー」
"Our Time Yellow"
「Genesis」
"Genesis"
[id:entity voices]
「暁闇エクステス」
"Gyouan Ex-tess"
「Run Back 'Round」
"Run Back 'Round"
「Slap by Step」
"Slap by Step"
「Fortune Spinner」
"Fortune Spinner"
「Hyper Jumpin'」
"Hyper Jumpin'"
「Dramatic XViltration」
"Dramatic XViltration"
「青春アーカイブ」
"Seishun Archive"
「夢見る空へ」
"Yumemiru Sora e"
「We are GAMERS !!!!」
"We are GAMERS !!!!"
「キラメキライダー☆」
"Kirameki Rider☆"
「電脳ぴゅお推し大宣言」
"Cyber Pyuo Oshi Great Declaration"
「Shiny Smily Story」
"Shiny Smily Story"
「Prism Melody」
"Prism Melody"
「Show Them (Who You Are)」
"Show Them (Who You Are)"
「All for One」
"All for One"
「DEV_IS COUNTDOWN メドレー2025」
"DEV_IS COUNTDOWN Medley 2025"
「Our Bright Parade」
"Our Bright Parade"
この後は もう1本グランプリ！
Coming up next: Mou Ippon Grand Prix!
2026年もホロライブプロダクションをよろしくお願い致します！
We look forward to your continued support for hololive production in 2026!